RG 161:001, Connecticut State Police
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. State Police Investigation Files, 1919-1998; 293.75 cubic feet
  - Hartford Circus Fire, 1941-1998; 4.5 cubic feet
    - 1987-094, 4.25 cubic feet
      - Top Tent Witnesses, A-G, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Top Tent Witnesses, J-W, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Out City Police Personnel, B-L, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Out City Police Personnel, M-W, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Case Reports – Miscellaneous, 1944-1953 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
      - Statements – Miscellaneous, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
      - Coroner’s Report, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - War Council Reports, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Weather Report, 1944 July 6 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Case Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
      - Unidentified Bodies, 1944-1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Unidentified Bodies – Little Miss 1565, 1944, 1963; photographs (Box 3, Folder 9)
        Contains Bob Glynn photographs of unidentified body, Little Miss 1565; Eleanor Cook and her brothers, suspected Little Miss 1565; Eleanor Cook and her mother, suspected Little Miss 1565.
      - Hartford Courant, 1944 July 7 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Photo reports, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - George Sanford Photographs, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 2)
        Contains big top and crowds before the fire; big top on fire.
        Still taken from original 8mm film.
      - Frank Shaw Photographs, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        Contains fire damaged bleachers and animal act cage; fire damaged bleachers (four photographs various views); fire damaged struts.
      - Carl Wallis Photographs, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        Contains tent burning (fourteen photographs various views); bleachers; monkey cages (two photographs); interior of tent and bleachers, before fire (two photographs).
      - Bob Glynn, Photographs of Unidentified Bodies, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        Contains unidentified bodies, does not included Little Miss 1565 (six photographs). Contains Graphic documentation of burn victims.
      - General Photographs, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 6)
        Contains midway (people leaving area after fire); firefighters; bleachers after fire with crowds standing nearby (two photographs).
      - General Photographs, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 7)
        Contains circus employees in court room; fire damaged circus equipment; two boys standing next to animal cages (after fire); police gathering evidence near animal cages; animal chutes (two photographs).
      - Armory Photographs, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        Contains temporary morgue; family reunited; people waiting to identify bodies; information desk.
      - Circus Employee Photographs, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 9)
        Contains circus employees helping injured man; circus employees reading newspapers with headline "135 Dead in Circus Fire"; circus employee hanging laundry near circus wagon; circus employee with children (prior to fire); circus employees sitting near circus wagon (prior to fire).
      - Hospital Photographs, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 10)
        Contains nurse feeding injured child; man bringing toys to injured child.
      - Bound reports, Sworn Statements of Circus Fire Witnesses, 1944 (Box 5)
      - Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
      - Suspect Files, 1944-1950; photographs (Box 6, Folder 3)
        Contains photographs of various suspects including: Floyd Gordon Cox, Floyd Washington Cox, Herman Cox, Wilson Cox, Gerald Cox, Junior Richard Cox, ___ Cox, Ralph A. Bever, Emmett Morrow Welch AKA Cox, and some unidentified suspects.
      - Suspect Files, 1944-1950 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Suspect Files, Cox AKA Emmett Welch, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
      - Suspect Files, Segee, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Suspect Files, Segee, 1950; 14 photographs (Box 6, Folder 8)
        Contains Robert Segee artwork.
      - Suspect Files, Segee, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
      - Suspect Files, Segee, 1950-1952 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Suspect Files, Segee, artwork, 1950; 5 photographs (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Suspect Files, Segee, artwork, 1950; 5 photographs (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Suspect Files, Segee, artwork, 1950; 4 photographs (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence-Miscellaneous, Aftermath, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence-Miscellaneous, Aftermath, 1944-1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Reports, 1941, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Restricted: Negatives and original materials removed due to preservation concerns (photocopies in files). (Box 9)
    - 2000-008, .25 cubic feet
      Records relating to the official re-examination of the Hartford Circus Fire.
      - Forensic Report, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Segee Interview, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        Contains a transcript and audio tapes.
      - Re-examination report, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1991, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Photographs, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Report of Captain William L. Schatzman of investigation of the Southbury Training School, 1943; 1 folder; 2002-065 (Box Shared box)
- Series 2. Commissioner Files, 1980-1985; 5.5 cubic feet
  - Donald J. Long, 1980-1985; 1987-043
    Arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - A&R Contract, 1984 (Box 74)
    - Administrative Purposes Only (Box 74)
    - Administrative Services, Dept of (Box 74)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 74)
    - Alumni Association (CT S.P. Academy Alumni) (Box 74)
    - Annual Report (Box 74)
    - Attorney General (Box 74)
    - Auditors of Public Accounts (Box 74)
    - Awards, recommendations for Department Awards (Box 74)
    - Biloon, S. correspondence (Box 74)
    - Biweekly Reports to Governor (Box 74)
    - Boards and Commissioners (re: Dept of Public Safety) (Box 74)
    - Board of Materials Review (Box 74)
    - Budget FY 1981-1982 (Box 74)
    - Budget FY 1982-1983 (Box 74)
    - Budget/Governor’s 1982-1983, Budget-in-Brief (Box 74)
    - Budget, 1982-1983, Firearms Permit, Examiners Office of Civil Preparedness, Military Dept, MPTC (Box 74)
    - Budget FY 1983-1984 (Box 74)
    - Budget, 1983-1984, MPTC (Box 75)
    - Budget, 1983-1984/Board of Firearms Permit Examiners (Box 75)
    - Case Preparation Fund (Box 75)
    - Chief State’s Attorney (Box 75)
    - Civil Preparedness, Office of (Box 75)
    - Civil Preparedness, Office of (Actions) (Box 75)
    - Civilian Personnel (Box 75)
    - Claims, against State (Insurance Claims and others) (Box 75)
    - Code of Ethics for Public Officials and State Employee (Guidelines) (Box 75)
    - Collect (Box 75)
    - Commission Demolition (Box 75)
    - Complaints (Box 75)
    - CT Conference on Municipalities (Box 75)
    - CT Justice Commission, 1981 (Box 75)
    - CT Justice Commission, 1982 (Box 75)
    - Connecticut Police Chiefs Association (Box 75)
    - CT Police Chiefs Association, “Labor Relations: Police Administrators Dilemma” (Box 75)
    - Connecticut Siting Council, 1981 (Box 75)
    - Connecticut Siting Council, 1982 (Box 76)
    - Connecticut Siting Council, Power Facility Evaluation Council (Box 76)
    - Correspondence – General (Box 76)
    - Council of Economic Affairs (Box 76)
    - Crane Operators, PA 81-321 (Box 76)
    - Data Processing (Box 76)
    - DCYS/Dept of Children and Youth Services (Box 76)
    - Discipline (Box 76)
    - Discrimination/Employment Practices (Box 76)
    - DOT, Department of Transportation (Box 76)
    - DOT/Highway User Costs in Connecticut (Box 77)
    - DOT/State Employees Ride Sharing Program (Box 77)
    - Education Dept Management Survey (Box 77)
    - Environmental Classification Document (Box 77)
    - Evaluations (Box 77)
    - Facility and Capital Plan (Statewide) (Box 77)
    - Financial Statement (Box 77)
    - Firearms Permit Examiners, Board of (Box 77)
    - Fire Marshal Bureau (Division of State Police) (Box 77)
    - Fire Prevention and Control, Commission on (Box 77)
    - Fire Study Bulletins/Commission on Fire Prevention and Control (Box 77)
    - Fiscal Office (Box 77)
    - Flex-Time Program (Box 77)
    - Forst, Lester – Deputy Commissioner (Box 77)
    - Fuel Contractor (Box 77)
    - General Assembly (Box 77)
    - Governor William A. O’Neill (Box 77)
    - Governor’s Arson Task Force (Box 78)
    - Governor’s Task Force on Regulatory Reform (Box 78)
    - Grants (Box 78)
    - Grasso, Ella (Memorial Statute Committee) (Box 78)
    - Hazardous Duty and/or Physical Hazardous Duty (Box 78)
    - Health Services, Dept of – Correspondence (Box 78)
    - Highway Statistics, 1980 (Box 78)
    - Human Resources, Dept of (Box 78)
    - IACP (Box 78)
    - Injured Employees (Box 78)
    - Inventory (Box 78)
    - Job Evaluation Program (Box 78)
    - Judicial Review, Council of Connecticut (Box 78)
    - Kiley, Robert vs. Dept of Public Safety (Box 78)
    - Labor Relations (Box 78)
    - Legislative Proposals (Box 78)
    - Management Info – Management Incentive Plan (MIP) (Box 78)
    - Meriden Complex (Box 78)
    - Miscellaneous Forms (Box 78)
    - Monthly Reports (Box 78)
    - MPTC, 1981 (Box 78)
    - MPTC, 1982 January-July (Box 79)
    - MPTC, 1982 August-December (Box 79)
    - MPTC/Trading Objectives (Box 79)
    - Mulligan, John – Lt. Colonel (Box 79)
    - National Safety Council (Box 79)
    - NESPAC (Box 79)
    - OPM, 1981 (Box 79)
    - OPM, 1981 (Box 79)
    - OPM/Conservation and Development Policies Plan, 1981-1985 (Box 79)
    - PAC (Police Association of Connecticut) (Box 79)
    - Pension Agreement, 1982 (Box 79)
    - Personnel Section (Dept of Public Safety) (Box 79)
    - Police Departments (Box 79)
    - Prison Overcrowding, Commission on, 1981 (Box 80)
    - Prison and Jail Overcrowding, Commission on, 1982 (Box 80)
    - Public Acts (Box 80)
    - Public Safety Departments/Out of State (Box 80)
    - Pursuit Training (Box 80)
    - Reports and Records (Box 80)
    - Resignation Information (Box 80)
    - Retirement (State Employees Retirement System) (Box 80)
    - Rogers, Frank – Attorney – Legal Advisor (Box 80)
    - Safety Education, Office of - Bureau Reports (Box 80)
    - Safety Education, Office of - Child Restraint Info (Box 80)
    - Safety Education, Office of - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 80)
    - Safety Education, Office of - Nelson Douglas, 1982 (Box 81)
    - Salary Survey (Box 81)
    - Scholarship Fund, Inc. – Connecticut Trooper’s Memorial (Box 81)
    - Selection Process, Sergeants etc. (Box 81)
    - Seniority Lists (DPS Div of SP) (Box 81)
    - Sick Leave (Box 81)
    - SOCITF (Box 81)
    - SPBI (Box 81)
    - Staff Report of Positions (Box 81)
    - State Agencies, Various (Box 81)
    - State Police, Division of – Miscellaneous (Box 81)
    - State Police Union (Box 81)
    - State Traffic Commission (STC), 1981 (Box 81)
    - State Traffic Commission (STC), 1982 January-June (Box 82)
    - State Traffic Commission (STC), 1982 July-December (Box 82)
    - State Traffic Commission (STC), Stamford, Commissioner Long (Box 82)
    - State Traffic Commission (STC), Danbury Project (Box 82)
    - State Traffic Commission (STC), Trumbull Shopping Park (Box 82)
    - Statewide Accident Reporting System (STAR) (Box 82)
    - Statewide Facility and Capitol Plan (Box 83)
    - Subpoenas/Summons (Box 83)
    - Suggestions (Employee Suggestion Committee) (Box 83)
    - Sunset Legislation re: Board of Firearms Permit Examiners (Box 83)
    - Sunset Legislation re: CJC (Box 83)
    - Sunset Legislation re: Fire Prevention and Control (Box 83)
    - Sunset Legislation re: Misc. Items (Box 83)
    - Sunset Legislation re: MPTC (Box 83)
    - Table of Organizations (Box 83)
    - Telecommunications (Box 83)
    - Towns – Correspondence (Box 83)
    - Training (SP Training) (Box 83)
    - Travel (Box 83)
    - Typewriter, Repair/Maintenance (Box 83)
    - UCR (Uniform Crime Report) (Box 83)
    - Valley Shore Emergency Communications (Box 84)
    - Vehicles (Box 84)
    - Workmen’s Compensation Guidelines (Box 84)
    - State Police Manuals: (Box 84)
      - Fuel Conservation Bulletins (Box 84)
      - In-Service Training Bulletins (Box 84)
      - Reports and Records Division Bulletins (Box 84)
      - Rules and Regulations (Box 84)
      - Traffic Division Bulletins (Box 84)
- Series 3. Connecticut State Police Troop A, 1923-1998; 35 cubic feet
  This entire series except for the roll call books and the warning log book is RESTRICTED per Connecticut General Statutes §54-142a.
  - 1989-031, 34 cubic feet
    - Call log books
      - 1923 January 6-1928 October 19, 8 volumes (Box 1)
        Includes miscellaneous newspapers of The Ridgefield Press.
      - 1928 October 20-1931 August 29, 8 volumes (Box 2)
      - 1931 August 30-1934 December 6, 4 volumes (Box 3)
      - 1934 December 7-1937 May 8, 4 volumes (Box 4)
      - 1937 May 8-1939 May 9, 4 volumes (Box 5)
      - 1939 May 9-1941 August 8, 4 volumes (Box 6)
      - 1941 August 8-1943 October 27, 4 volumes (Box 7)
      - 1943 October 28-1945 July 14, 5 volumes (Box 8)
      - 1945 July 15-1947 March 18, 7 volumes (Box 9)
      - 1947 March 19-1948 December 3, 9 volumes (Box 10)
      - 1948 December 3-1950 September 22, 9 volumes (Box 11)
      - 1950 September 23-1952 May 22, 9 volumes (Box 12)
      - 1952 May 22-1953 December 18, 9 volumes (Box 13)
      - 1953 December 18-1955 May 31, 9 volumes (Box 14)
      - 1955 June 1-1956 August 29, 8 volumes (Box 15)
      - 1956 August 29-1958 February 24, 6 volumes (Box 16)
      - 1958 February 24-1959 September 19, 6 volumes (Box 17)
      - 1959 September 19-1961 August 7, 6 volumes (Box 18)
      - 1961 August 7-1962 December 27, 6 volumes (Box 19)
      - 1962 December 27-1964 September 12, 6 volumes (Box 20)
      - 1964 September 12-1966 July 4, 6 volumes (Box 21)
      - 1966 July 4-1967 December 31, 6 volumes (Box 22)
      - 1968 January 1-1969 April 12, 6 volumes (Box 23)
      - 1969 April 12-1970 May 28, 6 volumes (Box 24)
      - 1970 May 28-1971 August 20, 6 volumes (Box 25)
      - 1971 August 21-1972 September 22, 6 volumes (Box 26)
      - 1972 September 22-1973 September 20, 6 volumes (Box 27)
      - 1973 September 20-1974 September 30, 8 volumes (Box 28)
      - 1974 October 1-1976 March 27, 8 volumes (Box 29)
      - 1976 March 28-1977 July 16, 6 volumes (Box 30)
      - 1977 July 16-1978 September 17, 6 volumes (Box 31)
      - 1978 September 17-1978 December 26, 1 volume (Box 32)
    - Case books
      - 1930 September 6-1961 June 30, 14 volumes (Box 33)
      - 1961 July 1-1979 September 9, 18 volumes (Box 34)
    - Roll call books
      - 1938 July 14-December 8, 1 volume (Box 5)
      - 1950 July-1964 December, 1 volume (Box 34)
    - Sub-station #2 log books
      - 1944 April 3-1945 July 5, 2 volumes (Box 8)
      - 1946 July 6, 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Supervisor's activity log books, 1974 July 2-1975 August 4; 2 volumes (Box 29)
    - Critical incident log books, 1978 November 27-1980 December 31; 10 volumes (Box 32)
    - Warning log book, 1953-1965 October 30; 1 volume (Box 33)
    - Service report case book, 1967 October 1-1968 December 31; 1 volume (Box 34)
  - 2013-028, 1 cubic foot
    - Arrest log books, 1993 January 1-1998 August 29; 6 volumes (Box 1)
- Series 4. Connecticut State Police Troop B, 1923-1998; 33.5 cubic feet
  This entire series is RESTRICTED per Connecticut General Statutes §54-142a.
  - 2013-036, 33 cubic feet
    - Call log books
      There is no box 25.
      - 1923 January 24-1932 November 2, 10 volumes (Box 1)
      - 1938 July 1-1941 July 2, 4 volumes (Box 2)
      - 1941 July 8-1944 April 27, 6 volumes (Box 3)
      - 1944 April 28-1946 November 28, 7 volumes (Box 4)
      - 1946 November 29-1948 December 7, 9 volumes (Box 5)
      - 1948 December 8-1950 May 15, 7 volumes (Box 6)
      - 1950 May 16-1951 October 7, 10 volumes (Box 7)
      - 1951 October 7-1953 February 14, 9 volumes (Box 8)
      - 1953 February 14-1954 May 30, 6 volumes (Box 9)
      - 1954 May 30-1955 October 24, 9 volumes (Box 10)
      - 1955 October 24-1957 April 15, 7 volumes (Box 11)
      - 1957 April 15-1958 September 26, 7 volumes (Box 12)
      - 1958 September 26-1960 September 2, 6 volumes (Box 13)
      - 1960 September 2-1962 August 5, 6 volumes (Box 14)
      - 1962 August 5-1964 May 8, 6 volumes (Box 15)
      - 1964 May 8-1965 September 25, 5 volumes (Box 16)
      - 1965 September 25-1966 December 31, 6 volumes (Box 17)
      - 1967 January 1-1968 May 12, 6 volumes (Box 18)
      - 1968 May 13-1969 June 3, 6 volumes (Box 19)
      - 1969 June 3-1970 June 8, 5 volumes (Box 20)
      - 1970 June 8-1971 August 14, 6 volumes (Box 21)
      - 1971 August 14-1972 October 27, 6 volumes (Box 22)
      - 1972 October 27-1973 December 31, 7 volumes (Box 23)
      - 1974 January 1-1974 July 1, 5 volumes (Box 24)
      - 1975 July 14-1976 June 12, 6 volumes (Box 26)
      - 1976 June 12-1977 May 31, 6 volumes (Box 27)
      - 1977 June 1-1978 May 19, 6 volumes (Box 28)
      - 1978 May 19-December 10, 4 volumes (Box 29)
    - Arrest log books
      - 1978 December 11-1983 September 3, 2 volumes (Box 29)
      - 1983 August 6-1994 December 4, 6 volumes (Box 30)
    - Resident trooper log books
      - 1962 June 11-1963 May 1, 7 volumes (Box 34)
      - 1966 September 1-1975 March 3, 1 volume (Box 31)
        Log book for the town of Kent.
      - 1984 March 1-1998 April 30, 3 volumes (Box 31)
    - Case books
      - 1951-1971, 19 volumes (Box 33)
      - 1971-1980, 14 volumes (Box 32)
  - 2014-022, .5 cubic feet
    - Assignment of complaints log books, 1932-1951; 2 volumes (Box 1)
- Series 5. Connecticut State Police Troop C, 1922-1999; 2013-026; 33 cubic feet
  - Call log books
    - 1922 August 22-1936 October 21, 13 volumes (Box 1)
    - 1925-1936, 4 volumes (Box 31)
    - 1936 October 21-1940 December 25, 7 volumes (Box 2)
    - 1940 December 26-1946 February 22, 4 volumes (Box 3)
    - 1946 February 22-1948 October 6, 7 volumes (Box 4)
    - 1948 October 7-1950 September 16, 8 volumes (Box 5)
    - 1950 September 17-1952 June 26, 8 volumes (Box 6)
    - 1952 June 26-1954 March 3, 6 volumes (Box 7)
    - 1954 March 3-1955 November 8, 5 volumes (Box 8)
    - 1955 November 8-1957 April 22, 6 volumes (Box 9)
    - 1957 April 22-1958 July 9, 6 volumes (Box 10)
    - 1958 July 9-1959 December 27, 6 volumes (Box 11)
    - 1959 December 27-1961 December 27, 5 volumes (Box 12)
    - 1961 December 27-1963 December 5, 6 volumes (Box 13)
    - 1963 December 5-1965 June 26, 5 volumes (Box 14)
    - 1965 June 26-1966 October 14, 5 volumes (Box 15)
    - 1966 October 14-1968 March 3, 5 volumes (Box 16)
    - 1968 March 3-1969 August 9, 6 volumes (Box 17)
    - 1969 August 9-1971 January 26, 5 volumes (Box 18)
    - 1971 January 26-1972 May 24, 5 volumes (Box 19)
    - 1972 May 24-1973 October 13, 6 volumes (Box 20)
    - 1973 October 14-1974 December 5, 6 volumes (Box 21)
    - 1974 December 5-1975 October 24, 6 volumes (Box 22)
    - 1975 October 24-1976 September 28, 6 volumes (Box 23)
    - 1976 September 29-1977 October 17, 6 volumes (Box 24)
    - 1977 October 17-1978 October 17, 6 volumes (Box 25)
    - 1978 October 17-1978 November 14, 1 volume (Box 26)
  - Arrest log books
    - 1978 November 14-1984 July 14, 4 volumes (Box 26)
    - 1984 July 14-1989 January 14, 5 volumes (Box 27)
    - 1989 January 15-1993 April 28, 6 volumes (Box 28)
    - 1993 April 28-1996 July 26, 6 volumes (Box 29)
    - 1996 July 25-1999 October 16, 6 volumes (Box 30)
  - Case books
    - 1930-1933, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - 1933-1941, 3 volumes (Box 31)
    - 1942-1965, 10 volumes (Box 32)
    - 1966-1974, 13 volumes (Box 33)
- Series 6. Connecticut State Police Troop D, 1940-2002; 31 cubic feet
  - 2003-024, 28 cubic feet
    - Call log books
      - 1940 January 1-1943 May 19, 9 volumes (Box 1)
      - 1943 May 19-1945 November 18, 8 volumes (Box 2)
      - 1945 November 19-1948 May 14, 10 volumes (Box 3)
      - 1948 May 15-1950 March 19, 8 volumes (Box 4)
      - 1950 March 19-1952 March 2, 8 volumes (Box 5)
      - 1952 March 2-1953 December 7, 9 volumes (Box 6)
      - 1953 December 8-1955 September 5, 9 volumes (Box 7)
      - 1955 September 5-1957 March 25, 7 volumes (Box 8)
      - 1957 March 25-1958 September 26, 6 volumes (Box 9)
      - 1958 September 26-1960 March 15, 6 volumes (Box 10)
      - 1960 March 16-1961 August 30, 6 volumes (Box 11)
      - 1961 August 30-1963 May 30, 6 volumes (Box 12)
      - 1963 December 31-1964 December 31, 6 volumes (Box 13)
      - 1964 December 31-1966 August 11, 6 volumes (Box 14)
      - 1966 August 12-1968 February 20, 6 volumes (Box 15)
      - 1968 February 20-1969 July 4, 6 volumes (Box 16)
      - 1969 July 4-1971 April 25, 6 volumes (Box 17)
      - 1971 April 25-1972 August 6, 6 volumes (Box 18)
      - 1972 August 7-1973 September 14, 6 volumes (Box 19)
      - 1973 September 14-1974 September 8, 6 volumes (Box 20)
      - 1974 September 8-1975 August 11, 6 volumes (Box 21)
      - 1975 August 12-1976 July 3, 6 volumes (Box 22)
      - 1976 July 3-1977 July 23, 6 volumes (Box 23)
      - 1977 July 23-1978 July 29, 6 volumes (Box 24)
      - 1978 July 29-November 24, 2 volumes (Box 25)
    - Critical incident log books, 1978 November 27-1979 November 26; 2 binders (Box 25)
    - Arrest log books
      - 1978 November 29-1987 July 30, 6 volumes (Box 26)
        First volume contains log book information for 1978 November 24-26.
      - 1987 July 30-1991 August 6, 6 volumes (Box 27)
      - 1991 August 6-1995 December 7, 6 volumes (Box 28)
  - 2013-027, 3 cubic feet
    - Case books, 1964-1977; 13 volumes (Box 1)
    - Arrest log books
      - 1995 December 7-1999 July 24, 5 volumes (Box 2)
      - 1999 July 24-2002 November 28, 5 volumes (Box 3)
- Series 7. Connecticut State Police Troop E, 1924-2000; 63 cubic feet
  This entire series except for the roll call book and officers' cases book is RESTRICTED per Connecticut General Statutes §54-142a.
  - 1989-030, 58 cubic feet
    - Case books
      - 1951 July 1-1971 December 31, 14 volumes (Box 1)
        Does not contain 1969-1970.
      - 1972 January 1-1978 November 14, 10 volumes (Box 2)
    - Roll call book, 1971 January 1-1977 January 4; 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Officers' cases book I, A-Mc, 1977-1978; 1 binder (Box 2)
    - Critical incident log books
      - 1978 November 15-1980 May 31, 19 volumes (Box 3)
      - 1980 June 1-1981 November 30, 18 volumes (Box 4)
      - 1981 December 1-1983 May 31, 19 volumes (Box 5)
      - 1981 June 1-1984 December 31, 18 volumes + loose court abstracts (Box 6)
        Does not contain 1983 July.
    - Arrest log books, 1978 November 15-1986 April 17; 7 volumes (Box 7)
      Does not contain 1985 January 31-August 14.
    - Call log books
      - 1924 January 1-1931 September 2, 12 volumes (Box 8)
        Does not include 1924 September 24-1925 May 31.
      - 1931 September 3-1934 October 5, 13 volumes (Box 9)
        Does not include 1933 October 18-1934 January 22.
      - 1934 October 5-1937 December 24, 12 volumes (Box 10)
      - 1937 December 25-1941 February 9, 10 volumes (Box 11)
      - 1941 February 10-June 15 (Volume Volume 1)
      - 1941 June 16-October 3 (Volume Volume 2)
      - 1941 October 3-1942 February 27 (Volume Volume 3)
      - 1942 February 27-July 21 (Volume Volume 4)
      - 1942 July 21-December 11 (Volume Volume 5)
      - 1942 December 11-1943 May 8 (Volume Volume 6)
      - 1943 May 8-August 24 (Volume Volume 7)
      - 1943 August 24-November 28 (Volume Volume 8)
      - 1943 November 29-1944 April 27 (Volume Volume 9)
      - 1944 April 27-August 25 (Volume Volume 10)
      - 1944 August 25-November 26 (Volume Volume 11)
      - 1944 November 26-1945 March 1 (Volume Volume 12)
      - 1945 March 1-June 9 (Volume Volume 13)
      - 1945 June 9-September 7 (Volume Volume 14)
      - 1945 September 7-1946 January 5 (Volume Volume 15)
      - 1946 January 5-May 9 (Volume Volume 16)